现在，乍一看，减少传输的负载
Now, at first glass, reducing the payload of each transfer, and
并且在需要的时候进行数据传输，貌似算是个办法
only transmitting data when it's required seems like a sound approach.
您减少数据的传输量，这样网络中的数据就少了。
You're reducing the amount of data being transferred, so that's less
这样在设备上所存储的运行过程中所产生的荣誉数据就少多了。
data on the network. That's less superfluous work being done storing processing
基本上在你没有真正的
data on the device. It's basically a case of putting off
知道你需要干什么之前，基本上都耽误着所有的工作。
any work, until you actually know you need to do it.
但事实证明相比于之前的大cookie模式下的全部工作，
But it turns out that this approach has it's drawbacks, compared
这种方法也有他的缺点。
to the big cookie model of all of that work up front.
所以，综上所述，这个还是一个更好的解决办法。但是让我们近距离观察这个大cookie
So, overall, this is a better solution. But let's take a closer look at the big
模板。要做到这一点，我们就需要
cookie model. And to do that, we really
底层的cell radio状态机。
need to understand the underlying cell radio state machine.